▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 1/4决赛
佩古拉 6-4 2-6 7-6(4) 阿尼西莫娃 · 赛后场上采访
And our set comes to an end.
这一盘结束了
A 2hour 15 match,
两小时十五分钟的比赛
but it's the same result again and again
结果却一次又一次
and again for Pigula against Anisimova.
一样 佩古拉对阿尼西莫娃
It's six love in terms
两人的交手战绩
of head-to-head meetings
已经来到
between the two good friends
六比零
on and off the court, but only one winner.
场下是朋友 场上只有一人赢
And it's a semifinal place
这是佩古拉
for the second time in three years in Cincy
三年两次杀进辛辛那提半决赛
for Jesse Beula edging the tie break
决胜盘抢七
against Anisimo.
险胜阿尼西莫娃
I will survive and you did by just the skin
我一定会活下来
of your teeth.
而你这次是死里逃生
Jess, how does it feel to get
杰西 这么艰难的一场
through a tough match like that?
拿下来是什么感觉？
Yeah, I mean Amanda's an amazing player,
阿曼达是个很厉害的球员
an amazing ball striker.
击球质量特别高
I know that I have a good record
我知道我对她战绩不错
against her, but it literally every single
但基本上
match is pretty much like it was today.
每一场都打得像今天这样
So, I know that I have to, like you say,
所以就像你说的那样
try and survive.
我得想办法活下来
Sometimes she can play lights out tennis
她状态好的时候真的打不过
where there's not much you can do like
你什么都做不了
in the second set.
像第二盘那样
But I think I was able
但我觉得我
to to start getting some momentum
在那一盘快结束时
at the end of that set and then take it
找回了一点势头
into the third and kind of get ahead,
带进决胜盘 慢慢占了上风
but it was still wasn't enough.
但那还不够
But, I got there.
好在最后拿下来了
It was a go big or go home match.
这是一场孤注一掷的比赛
You came out the third set,
决胜盘一开始
looks like you were taking the ball like a half
你出手好像提前了
a second earlier in order to get ahead,
半秒 想要抢占先机
but then if you blink your eyes,
但只要一眨眼
she catches back up.
她又追回来了
What do you think was the key today?
今天赢球的关键是什么？
It really was just a game of margins
真的就是分毫之差的较量
and a big butterfly just flew onto my head
一只大蝴蝶刚刚飞到我头上
in that interview.
就在这段采访里
Yeah, I it's like you said,
没错 就像你说的那样
I I really have to not let her ball play me,
我真的不能被她的球牵着走
but I'm pretty sure she's one
她应该是巡回赛里
of the if not the hardest hitter on tour,
击球最重的那几个人之一
so that's very hard to do.
所以这真的很难做到
But I I think it's one of my skills
但我觉得这正是我
that I'm pretty good at.
比较擅长的一项能力
So, you really have to to not let
不能让她
her push you around the court.
把你满场调动
And when you do, you kind
一旦被她牵着走
of have to absorb the pace and do as much
就得尽量卸掉她的力量
as you can to kind of not let her set up
不能让她轻易架起
and and rip her shots,
打出那种重炮
which again is very, very hard.
这同样非常难
So, yeah, I was trying
所以我就想着
to play a little bit more aggressive,
打得更主动一点
get my feet, get my body weight kind
让脚步和身体重心
of moving into the court a little bit
更往场内压一点
at the start of the third,
决胜盘一开局就这么打
and I think I started playing much better.
感觉状态一下就上来了
Next up, Iga or Elena.
下一轮 斯瓦泰克或莱巴金娜
A, will you watch tonight?
你今晚会看这场球吗？
and be you're one of the few players
你可是少数
who has been able to beat both of them
两个人都赢过的球员
before.
之一
Although they are tough ones.
虽然她们都不好打
Yeah, I mean I haven't beaten them
不过我今年
this year so it's it's always a tough task
还没赢过她们 一直很难打
but hey they're the top players.
但她们确实是顶尖选手
You know we're all top 10.
我们都排在前十
I think the rankings honestly
老实说我觉得排名
to me don't mean much.
对我来说没那么重要
I think
其实
we're we're barely separated out here
站到场上
when we come out on the court.
大家其实差不了多少
Everyone is really tough.
每个人都很难对付
So it's going to be a great match tonight.
今晚这场应该会很精彩
I'm sure I'll tune in and try my best
我肯定会看 也会尽量
to recover.
好好恢复一下
All right. We wish you the best of luck.
祝你好运
Ladies and gentlemen, Jessica Pagoula.
有请 杰西卡·佩古拉